KAROLINA JEDRZEJAK Software Developer

CONTACT

phone: 778 776 1417

Linkedln: www.linkedin.com/in/kjedrzejak/
e-mail: kjedrzejak91@gmail.com

website: https://k-jedrzejak.github.io/portfolio/

location: 102Ave, Maple Ridge BC

PROFILE

With over 5 years of experience in front-end development, specializing in building web applications using React.js and Vue.js. Consistently deliver improved performance and user satisfaction, with ongoing skills enhancement to stay current with industry trends and technologies.

SKILLS

Soft: Communication, Teamwork, Adaptability, Curiosity, Critical thinking, Accountability, Time management, Attention to detail

Technical: TypeScript / Vue.js / React.js / Next.js / CSS3 (Less / Sass) / NoSQL & SQL Databases / Jest.js / Cypress / GIT / Rest API / Responsive Web Design / Cross-Browser Compatibility / Photoshop / Figma

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Developer CE Solutions, Hinton, Canada

08/2023 - 06/2024

- Proficient in Vue.js and React.js for web app development, including logistics management platforms, alongside mobile app development
 using Flutter. Executed Jest.js unit tests and optimized database queries and REST API calls, boosting performance by about 40%
- Led critical project enhancements, optimizing code for a 30% performance boost and improving user experience. Also spearheaded UI/UX-aligned design and implemented new functionalities for enhanced application responsiveness.

JavaScript Developer Adrino Mobile, Warsaw, Poland

12/2022 - 08/2023

- Developed unique mobile ads with mini-games using JavaScript, TypeScript, and CSS3 increased campaign revenue by about 60% compared to static ads.
- Lead frontend developer for a platform managing publishers and advertisements. Managed tasks, conducted code reviews. Utilized TypeScript, React.js, and Next.js.
- Implemented TypeScript for advertising projects, which accelerated the creation process by 50%.

Magento2 Frontend Developer Aurora Creation, Bialystok, Poland

02/2021 - 12/2022

- · Developed Progressive Web Applications using React.js integrated with Magento 2 platform European brands.
- Led 35% of company projects as Head Frontend Developer: managed team tasks, collaborated with clients and project managers, implemented Magento2 training programs, and conducted code reviews.

Frontend Developer Euro-Net, Warsaw, Poland

08/2019 - 02/2021

 Implemented promotional product landing pages with JavaScript, CSS3, and FreeMarker significantly boosted online sales and traffic to manufacturers' direct websites.

Junior Frontend Developer Praca.pl, Warsaw, Poland

03/2019 - 08/2019

 Developed custom landing pages using JavaScript, PHP, and CSS3, significantly increasing daily user traffic to the praca.pl homepage through effective SEO strategies.

EDUCATION

Computer Science Bialystok Technical University, Bialystok, Poland

2017-2019

· Completed 2 years of a 3.5-year program

Management and Production Engineering Bialystok Technical University, Bialystok, Poland

2010-2014

· Bachelor's degree